VO CHI LONG

BACKEND DEVELOPER



CONTACT



1 0833 28 04 01



vochilong.work@gmail.com



https://github.com/longaodai



https://hioncoding.com/about

PROFILE

I am a Software Developer with over 3 years of website development experience

Always learn and learn new knowledge to develop and improve yourself Desire to have a long-term job and be able to contribute a lot of value to the company

SKILLS

Back-end: PHP / Laravel / Codeigniter / Yii2, MySQL, NodeJS / ExpressJS, Python / Flask / FastAPI

Front-end: HTML, CSS / Bootstrap, Javascript / Jquery / VueJS

Other: Docker, Git / Github, CI/CD Github actions, Ubuntu, Config Apache / Nginx, Generative Al. ...

SOFT SKILLS

- Communication skills
- Teamwork, independent work
- · Workflow management
- Project structure design

WORK EXPERIENCE

HYBRID TECHNOLOGIES CO., LTD

9/2021 - Present

Position: Back-end Developer

- Build and develop the website for Japanese Wifi rental / ESIM, booking car Airport-Taxi, website camping car rental Japanese, website admin manages data request ticket train.
- Build and develop a live chat website.
- Design and implement RESTful API to support generative AI functions, connecting to large language models such as OpenAI, Gemini, Anthropic,...
- Participate in implementing CI/CD refactoring for the project using Github action, AWS ECR....

BANG TRUONG TRADING & SERVICE CO., LTD

1/2021 - 8/2021

Position: Back-end Developer

- Build and develop a website for user data management, and a website for buying cars
- Build and develop WordPress website.

EDUCATION

FPT POLYTECHNIC DA NANG

2019 - 2021

Graduated in Information technology

PROJECT PARTICIPATED

9/2021 - Present

ADMIN | API MANAGES SHINKANSEN TRAIN TICKET BOOKING REQUESTS

- **Position:** Developer member
- **Responsibilities:** Analyze customer requirements, code API, and handle the functional interface on the admin side.
- Technologies used: PHP/Yii2, HTML, CSS, Javascript, ReactJS, MySQL
- Project description: The website manages train ticket booking requests for administrators, helping administrators easily manage, release, cancel, etc... tickets.
 The API handles data sent from third parties.

JAPAN WIRELESS - WIFI RENTAL / ESIM WEBSITE

- **Position:** Developer member
- **Responsibilities:** Analyze customer requirements, code API and handle the functional interface on the admin side and the user side.
- Technologies used: PHP/Laravel, HTML, Css, Javascript, TS, VueJS, MySQL
- **Project description:** The website for people around the world who need to rent wifi internet service when traveling or working in Japan.

GLOBAL MOBILE WIFI RENTAL WEBSITE PROJECT

- **Position:** Developer member
- **Responsibilities:** Analyze customer requirements, code API, and handle the functional interface on the admin side.
- Technologies used: PHP/Laravel, HTML, CSS, Javascript, ReactJS, MySQL
- **Project description:** The website for people around the world who need to rent wifi internet service when traveling or working in Japan.

JAPAN BOOKING AIRPORT TAXI WEBSITE

- **Position:** Developer member
- **Responsibilities:** Analyze customer requirements, code API and handle the functional interface on the admin side and the user side.
- Technologies used: PHP/Laravel, HTML, CSS, Javascript, Vuejs, MySQL
- **Project description:** The website for people around the world when they need to book a car from the airport to a location, a hotel, or a location to the airport in Japan.

JAPAN RV CAMPING CAR RENTAL WEBSITE

- **Position:** Developer member
- **Responsibilities:** Analyze customer requirements, code API and handle the functional interface on the admin side and the user side.
- Technologies used: PHP/Laravel/Codeigniter3, HTML, CSS, Javascript, Vuejs, MySQL, Python
- **Project description:** The website to book camping car rentals for people around the world when there is a need for travel vehicles in Japan.

LIVE CHAT WEBSITE PROJECT

- **Position:** Developer member
- **Responsibilities:** Analyze customer requirements, and code and handle the functional interface on the admin and the user side.
- Technologies used: Vuejs, Reactjs, Supabase, AWS Amplify, GraphQL
- **Project description:** The website supports admins in managing incoming messages and communicating with users via live chat, helping users solve questions during the use of the main website (website-embedded live chat).

MIDWARE - AI AGENTS & WORKSPACE FOR EVERYONE

- **Position:** Developer member
- **Responsibilities:** Designed and implemented RESTful APIs to support Generative AI functionalities, connect with models: OpenAI, Gemini, Anthropic
- Technologies used: Python/FastAPI, Langchain, PostgreSQL
- Project description: The website is an intuitive AI workspace designed to boost productivity. It enables you to create custom AI agents quickly and effortlessly using powerful generative AI capabilities.

1/2021 - 8/2021

WEBSITE MANAGE, ANALYZE SALES DATA

- **Position:** Developer member (Project 1 member)
- **Responsibilities:** Analyze customer requirements, build architecture, and code, and handle the functional interface for the admin site.
- Technologies used: PHP/Laravel, Html, Css, Javascript, Jquery, Bootstrap
- **Project description:** The website handles user information, then analyzes and share the data for remarketing telesales staff.

JAPAN USED CAR BUYING WEBSITE

- **Position:** Developer member
- **Responsibilities:** Analyze customer requirements, build architecture, and code, and handle the functional interface for the admin, client site.
- Technologies used: NodeJS/ExpressJS, HTML, CSS, SCSS, Javascript, Jquery, Bootstrap, MySQL
- **Project description:** The website receives and processes user and vehicle information. Then transfers the information to the administrator for distribution to the nearest headquarters for processing.

COMMUNITY CONTRIBUTION

REPOSITORY-PATTERN

My package support generator repository pattern for Laravel Github: https://github.com/longaodai/repository-pattern

PACKAGE SSH SERVER

My package support ssh server for auto deploy in Github actions Github: https://github.com/longaodai/ssh-server

HION FRAMEWORK

Hion is a simple PHP framework (is in development stage)

Github: https://github.com/longaodai/Hion

HION CODING BLOG

Hion Coding is a personal blog specializing in programming and the most miscellaneous things in life.

Website: https://hioncoding.com